<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text App</string>
    <string name="article_title">Florence Welch\'s tribute</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Florence Welch has revealed the song Florence Welch has revealed the song Florence Welch has revealed the song</string>
    <string name="article_text">Florence Welch (www.florencewelch.com) has paid tribute to Patti Smith in a brand new song.\n \nThe Florence + The Machine front woman  has opened up about the group\'s latest album <b>\'High As Hope\'</b>, and revealed the track \'Patricia\' was inspired by the iconic singer songwriter.

Speaking to Jo Whiley on BBC Radio 2, the 31-year-old star said: \"I\'ve always loved her and it was actually through her writing that I feel I really got to know her.\n\n\"She writes about life in such a beautiful way that it seems to endow even the smallest things with a sense of spirituality or reverence.

\"Whether it\'s going to the coffee shop or what you eat for breakfast in the morning... She kind of elevates everything and it was like a little north star to follow as like how to have a creative life as a whole.\"\n\nHowever, Florence did point out that the track is not entirely written about punk poet Patti, 71, but didn\'t reveal the other influences.

She laughed: \"There is a bit in the middle of the song that definitely isn't about her.\"\n\nMeanwhile, the singer - whose band released its fourth studio album on June 29 - recently revealed that her mother wasn\'t keen on her pursuing music as a career.\n

The group\'s debut album <i>\'Lungs\'</i> topped the UK charts eight years ago, but it took a while for Evelyn Kathleen Welch to come to terms with her daughter\'s path.\n

As Professor of Renaissance Studies and Vice-Principal for Arts and Sciences at King\'s College London, Florence\'s mum was disappointed she didn\'t go to university.\n

Speaking to The Observer magazine, Florence said: \"My mum was so worried about me doing music - she thought it was dangerous, could hurt me, could be fleeting.\n

\"She\'s accepted it\'s not a phase now. But she\'s been through a lot, so always prepares for the worst.\"</string>
</resources>
